webpackJsonp([65856866535745],{474:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function r(e){return e&&e.__esModule?e:{default:e}}function i(e,a){if(!(e instanceof a))throw new TypeError("Cannot call a class as a function")}function o(e,a){if(!e)throw new ReferenceError("this hasn't been initialised - super() hasn't been called");return!a||"object"!=typeof a&&"function"!=typeof a?e:a}function n(e,a){if("function"!=typeof a&&null!==a)throw new TypeError("Super expression must either be null or a function, not "+typeof a);e.prototype=Object.create(a&&a.prototype,{constructor:{value:e,enumerable:!1,writable:!0,configurable:!0}}),a&&(Object.setPrototypeOf?Object.setPrototypeOf(e,a):e.__proto__=a)}a.__esModule=!0;var l=t(1),s=r(l),c=t(23),d=r(c),u=t(32),m=(r(u),t(43)),p=r(m),f=t(50),h=r(f),b=[{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"1Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-1",href:"#collapse-1",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"2Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-2",href:"#collapse-2",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"3Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-3",href:"#collapse-3",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"4Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-4",href:"#collapse-4",display:!0},{question:"How do I edit a page?",answer:"5Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-5",href:"#collapse-5",display:!0},{question:"Why was my article deleted?",answer:"6Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-6",href:"#collapse-6",display:!0},{question:"How do I change the name of an article?",answer:"7Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-7",href:"#collapse-7",display:!0}],y=[{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"1Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-1",href:"#collapse-tab2-1",display:!0},{question:"Who owns Wikipedia?",answer:"2Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-2",href:"#collapse-tab2-2",display:!0},{question:"Why am I having trouble logging in?",answer:"3Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-3",href:"#collapse-tab2-3",display:!0},{question:"How can I contact Wikipedia?",answer:"4Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-4",href:"#collapse-tab2-4",display:!0},{question:"How do I delete my account?",answer:"5Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-5",href:"#collapse-tab2-5",display:!0},{question:"Who writes the articles on Wikipedia?",answer:"6Anim pariatur cliche reprehenderit, enim eiusmod high life accusamus terry richardson ad squid. 3 wolf moon officia aute, non cupidatat skateboard dolor brunch.",id:"collapse-tab2-6",href:"#collapse-tab2-6",display:!0}],w=(b.reverse(),y.reverse(),function(e){return s.default.createElement("div",{className:"card"},s.default.createElement("div",{className:"card-header panel-heading",role:"tab",id:"headingOne"},s.default.createElement("a",{role:"button",className:"collapsed text-black","data-toggle":"collapse","data-parent":"#accordion","data-core":"",href:e.href,"aria-expanded":"false","aria-controls":"collapse1"},s.default.createElement("p",{className:"lead black display-5 mr-3"},s.default.createElement("span",{className:"sign mbr-iconfont mbri-arrow-down inactive"})," ",e.question))),s.default.createElement("div",{id:e.id,className:"panel-collapse noScroll collapse",role:"tabpanel","aria-labelledby":"headingOne"},s.default.createElement("div",{className:"panel-body p-4"},s.default.createElement("p",{className:"mbr-fonts-style panel-text display-7"},e.answer))))}),q=b.map(w),g=q.slice(0,5),E=y.map(w),k=E.slice(0,5),N=function(e){function a(){return i(this,a),o(this,e.apply(this,arguments))}return n(a,e),a.prototype.render=function(){return s.default.createElement("div",{className:"pt-5 pb-1 mb-2",id:"content-14"},s.default.createElement(h.default,{title:"Questions",breadcrumbItem1:"Home",breadcrumbItem2:"FaQ"}),s.default.createElement("div",{className:"container pt-5 pb-5"},s.default.createElement("div",{className:"f_rht ml-3 mr-3 mb-5 text-center"},s.default.createElement("h2",{className:"feat-title"},"Frequently Asked Questions"),s.default.createElement("span",{className:"lead black"},"Here are the most frequently asked questions at ZenForce. If you have a question not answered here - or throughout our webiste - please ",s.default.createElement(d.default,{className:"",to:"./contact"},"Contact Us"),".")),s.default.createElement("div",{className:"row pb-5"},s.default.createElement("div",{className:"col-lg-8 col-md-10 col-sm-12 mx-auto"},s.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2"},"Product"),s.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),g,s.default.createElement("h1",{className:"faq mb-2 mt-5"},"Sales"),s.default.createElement("hr",{className:"mt-3 mb-4"}),k))),s.default.createElement(p.default,null))},a}(l.Component);a.default=N,e.exports=a.default}});
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-fa-q-js-e5645b83537a231002fa.js.map